[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hopkins"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well, especially in this country because they usually get it wrong, say Sir Hopkins.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, first of all, I looked at the script and I thought I don't want to do another weirdo, because I'm not - wasn't quite sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Was that what grabbed you, that it had happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gary Thomas"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "But you believe there is a devil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, we had - I'll preface this by saying that, we had Father Gary Thomas, who is an exorcist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "And he was your expert on the film, was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "So what do you think of my - my Latin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I thought it was quite impressive, given it's now forgotten and all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "You?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP"], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "How much of that is - is you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "It's all me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "You put that in there, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "EX", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "And is that - and is that because you actually - that's really what you believe yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "That's what I believe in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Do you believe in God?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "You don't like absolutism, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "You think that's dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think it is dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "You know, what do you make of that phenomenon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, the safest answer I can give is I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "He's done this, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "He's done it, and he says some extraordinary things do happen, extrasensory perception things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Would you believe this movie if you didn't pretty more (ph) believe in this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RBR", ":", "NN", ":", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "No, I can't have a cynicism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What changed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Oh, something, a crisis in my life, some 35 years ago, and I was hell bent on destruction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "So it's a fact that you, in that moment, as an atheist, you decided to pray to God, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "OPKINS: Oh, I - I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "I mean, can you - can you still do it, with the same sinister face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Oh, dear God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "You want me to do it again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Did you still get asked to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "In a way, it's become almost your catch phrase?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Do you actually drink - do you ever drink Chianti?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Have you ever eat fava beans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "It was one of the greatest terrifying characters ever, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 310, "question": "It's the whole thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "They asked me the other day -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Any vices?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Yes, any vices.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "You don't smoke, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Or do you feel you've had your great feeling of exercising (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I have had everything taken out of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "So you become more ruthless these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "It's not ruthless.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Are you - are you at peace with yourself these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Do you still have that burning drive to achieve, to get the acclaim of your peer group?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "OPKINS: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What would be the moment you'd replay, right now, if you have the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Ah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "At that moment when you're sitting there and you - how many times have you been nominated before that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "That's my first nomination.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What's going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I didn't think I was going to get it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Was that - was that the greatest rush you've ever experienced?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Incredible actors you're up against, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Oh, yes, the greatest in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What - when you're standing there, because I'm - I'm unlikely to ever get this moment, when you're standing there, who were you thinking of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I've been thinking of my father, because he died 10 years previous, on that very night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "What would he have made of that minute you're there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "He probably smoked himself to death because he always smokes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Are you - are you perturbed (ph) by this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Who to you have been the greatest actors of all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Past, present and -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Is he - is he the greatest living actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I think he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brando", "Betty Davis"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "What do you look for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Oh, I think the power of somebody like Brando or De Niro or Betty Davis, you know, going back through time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "They have a grasp of everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Damon"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Who do you see of the younger crop today that have - that may have that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "DiCaprio certainly and I think I'm a great fan of Matt Damon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Are you drawn to the darker art?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "No, it's not - it's not that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Is it - where it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "It should be - it's quite a large town.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "The population of it would be what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "OPKINS: When I was born it's about 75,000, a lot smaller.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How much more time did it bring you as a good actor, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, I thought it was just the thing you did was just to drink and get smashed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Do all great actors have to have some kind of demon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I think you have to be -- yes, I think you have to have a bit of trouble in your life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Does it give you the kind of tormented face that you need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "It gives you the drive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Do you like -- do you like being famous now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Yes, it's fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "I tell you -- can I tell you a quick story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jodie Foster"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Which of the actresses do you really most admire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Without a doubt, Jodie Foster.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Do you stay in touch with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "None at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "None at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "You didn't suddenly start doing your little Hannibal act for old time's sake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I just obey orders.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Have you got better at marriage as you've got older?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "If you had your time again -- this is your third marriage, would you have played things differently in your previous marriages?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "You can't go back and second guess yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Why do you love America so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I think it was just something to do with the post-war years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Steven Tyler and Jennifer Lopez with Randy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "They're terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Tyler", "Jennifer Lopez", "Randy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Do you miss a bit of that grit though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Isn't Randy one of your mates?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Randy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Is he your only famous friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "He's my only famous friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["two years ago"]}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Do you go to the Oscars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "I went about two years ago, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Does it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "I don't know what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Is that one of the reasons you live out in Malibu?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Yes, as far away from --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Malibu"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Is there a lot of phoniness really that does on in the business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Well, I'm not going to say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Do you think there's been a sort of breakdown in priorities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "If I wrote my own epitaph, it would be -- well, first of all, do you know Mel Blanc, the vocal guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "ORGAN: Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mel Blanc"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "Because what we are about to see, Michelle, is your mother actually undergoing an exorcism for real, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Are these -- are these classic signs of somebody who has been, in your view, possessed by the devil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "I mean, it must have been, as a daughter, just almost unbearable to watch this, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "It's a nightmare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Was there a time when your mother was perfectly normal or did she always have this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Do you remember the first time it happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "Oh, yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "How old were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Fifteen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 799, "question": "And it was a similar scene to the one we witnessed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "Yes, actually that looked like one of the first ones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe that she was possessed by the devil or evil spirits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "So I guess the obvious question is, why would this happen to somebody like Patty (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Pat Reading was an exception.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patty"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "-- and she had 16 of these incidents where you had to bring a priest in, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 846, "question": "When she came around, did she have any memory of what had happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 847, "answer": "No memory at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Were you honest with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "In the beginning, I didn't want to tell her everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "Did you show her the video?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "I don't believe that one, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "I mean, so for people who are watching this who may have a similar situation going on in their homes, how should they deal with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "Basically, rule everything out from a medical perspective, a psychological perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "Do you believe that they're linked in some way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "She had what they believe was pancreatic cancer or colon cancer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "I mean, why should people bother, John, in having these if they're not going to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Well, the key factor with this is very seldomly (ph) an exorcism or a deliverance is very successful on one try.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}]